

FAOCCI LAYUG

GRAPHIC DESIGNER, WEB DESIGNER, COMPUTER TECHNICIAN



+63 909-122-6365





in linkedin.com/in/faocci



fgl.netlify.app



Mabalacat City, Pampanga

Hello, I'm Faocci Ghaize O. Layug, a tech and design enthusiast ready to bring my expertise to your projects. With a knack for creative problem-solving in web and graphic design, and a solid foundation in computer technology, I'm excited to contribute to a team that values innovation and excellence. Let's make a positive impact in the digital sphere together!

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer Self Employed

Mabalacat City Pampanga, Philippines

2016 - Present

Computer Technician Self Employed

Mabalacat City Pampanga, Philippines

2014 - Present

Project Manager (Capstone) Mabalacat City College

Dolores, Mabalacat City Pampanga, Philippines

2023 - 2024

Web Designer (SHS Capstone): Children Of Fatima School Inc.

San Francisco, Mabalacat City, Philippines

2019 - 2020

EDUCATION

College **Bachelor of Science Information Technology**

Mabalacat City College

2020 - 2024

Information Communication Technology Senior High

Children of Fatima Inc.

2018 - 2020

Junior High Madapdap, Mabalacat City Pampanga

2023 - 2024

SKILLS

Web Design : Proficient in HTML, CSS, and introductory JavaScript

for creating and styling web pages. Familiar with

principles of responsive design.

Graphic Design : Skilled in using graphic design tools such as Adobe

Photoshop for image editing and Adobe Illustrator for

vector graphics.

Computer Literate: Proficient in operating systems (Windows, MacOS),

Microsoft Office Suite, internet navigation, basic troubleshooting, hardware installation, software troubleshooting, and network configuration.

CERTIFICATIONS

Introduction to Packet Tracer

- Introduction to Networks
- Introduction to Cybersecurity
- Cybersecurity Essentials
- Advanced Search Engine Optimization
- SEO Tutorial for Beginners
- Introduction to SEO Fundamentals Training
- Introduction to HTML
- Introduction to CSS

- Introduction to PHP
- Introduction to SQL
- Introduction to Graphic Design; Basics of UI/UX
- Introduction to the Fundamentals of Databases
- Introduction to Artificial Intelligence
- Machine Learning
- Introduction to Front End Development

REFFERENCE

Available upon request.

I hereby certify that all above information is true and correct to the best of my knowledge and ability

FAOCCI GHAIZE O. LAYUG

APPLICANT/SIGNATURE